{"data":{"createNewExamAttempt":{"attempt":{"id":"791ff061-c096-4e20-ab22-d12918fd559e"},"exam":{"id":"dde70475-6381-4703-82af-ad7e597b6396","title":"AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam","duration":5400,"totalQuestions":65,"questions":[{"id":"h0bz8vyv-zk25-7xf6-p1l3-v0qntk7m5yjw","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are types of cloud computing deployments?","explanation":"The three types of cloud deployments are: \r\n Public - where everyone and anyone can access that cloud's resources \r\n Private - also called on-premises where the underlying cloud infrastructure is owned and operated by a private entity for the sole use of that entity \r\n Hybrid - which is a mix of both. \r\n Mixed cloud is not a term used to describe a cloud computing deployment","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/types-of-cloud-computing/","title":"Types of Cloud Computing"}],"answers":[{"id":"7d22e2d665f6d51244a33f26e96904f9","text":"Mixed cloud","correct":false},{"id":"2dde6ce98c19e445f3c47a7a9d166f04","text":"Hybrid cloud","correct":true},{"id":"761883c0d5c55fba5b200ac8ac0d86e5","text":"Public cloud","correct":true},{"id":"cb38b39495aded16d3565297386a9c9e","text":"Private cloud","correct":true}]},{"id":"riqpy09p-2mos-4v71-m59a-je7iknttb5c4","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following is generally not billed for on the AWS platform?","explanation":"Data Transferred in to AWS is almost always free of charge (excluding large transfer services, like AWS Snowball). The reason for this, and best way to remember it is that AWS don't mind you transferring lots of data in to their services, since you'll already be paying to use and store it.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/pricing/","title":"AWS Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"72a2694d2bcec74cfbc3e76e2e8d6c24","text":"Data-in","correct":true},{"id":"8c4aa541ee911e8d80451ef8cc304806","text":"Storage","correct":false},{"id":"a5227beaedc6d59181cd9199f25d32ce","text":"Data-out","correct":false},{"id":"a623a8d0366bf079411aa30be45b2d10","text":"Compute","correct":false}]},{"id":"32c7f1bb-425d-4d33-b870-b88f89ef9f08","domain":"security","question":"An oil and gas utility company which is highly regulated must create a cloud governance scheme. The company is organized into multiple autonomous departments which will all be using AWS resources. These departments each sponsor independent projects that are reviewed by regulatory boards for the approval of customer price increases. The code and infrastructure for each project has production, development, and testing environments. Which of the following account strategies will maximize security and operational efficiency for the company?","explanation":"A multi-layered account structure will work best for this company, leveraging AWS Organizations to establish Organizational Units for each department, and separate production, development, and testing environments. While there is no physical AWS account at the department level, Service Control Policies can be applied at the Organizational Unit level, and billing can be reported separately for each department. An account for each department, in which the department combines dev/test/and prod, or a single account for the company hosting all workloads together will NOT provide for segregation of production, development, and testing environments at the account level. Multiple standalone accounts for each department and environment would compromise operational efficiency in managing environments across departments as there is no overarching AWS Organization to manage all the accounts centrally.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/Security/AWS_Security_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"AWS Security Best Practices"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/organizations/","title":"AWS Organizations"}],"answers":[{"id":"6773420477c1653d8837f13bfa8ec24d","text":"Create a single AWS account for centralized security management","correct":false},{"id":"281f961ca6e4d83f6570979548ba64e2","text":"Create multiple AWS accounts, one for the production environment, one for the development environment, and one for the testing environment for all departments","correct":false},{"id":"e4be6081f1a5dc1cc67c1a4633121580","text":"Create an Organization Unit structure in AWS Organizations with separate underlying accounts for production, development, and testing environments","correct":true},{"id":"bb38e2c475c21f60a71674d4dd27ff93","text":"Create multiple AWS accounts, one for each autonomous department within the company","correct":false}]},{"id":"e08137aa-20a0-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following describes a subnet?","explanation":"A virtual private cloud, or VPC, is the virtual network you create in your AWS account. When you create a VPC, you split it into smaller network segments by specifying a range of IP addresses. These segments are referred to as subnets, and this is where you launch your AWS resources.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/what-is-amazon-vpc.html","title":"What Is Amazon VPC?"}],"answers":[{"id":"5e57bdce4ee3d720c44022ab3a1989dc","text":"A virtual network dedicated to an AWS account","correct":false},{"id":"341f92e23cc01405941735e106cc5b82","text":"A range of IP addresses in the virtual private cloud","correct":true},{"id":"79da4a3447f86eaa72f611a8d8a1d4cc","text":"A private connection to the virtual private cloud","correct":false},{"id":"35b8947d693a814719c463b699fee868","text":"A subsection of the Internet","correct":false}]},{"id":"5ayciun1-a7hg-i7yq-4oeq-elwlon69tcex","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below terms represents a series of Edge Locations plus information about how you want content managed as part of a CDN?","explanation":"A Distribution is made up of Edge Locations that you want to serve content from, and details about how that content will be tracked an managed. Edge Groups and Circulations are not CloudFront Concepts, and although Load Balancer is an AWS service that helps you direct web traffic, it is not applicable in this case.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudFront/latest/DeveloperGuide/distribution-working-with.html","title":"Working with Distributions"}],"answers":[{"id":"59e3676a32b06a177d0617fde3d2ca48","text":"An Edge Group","correct":false},{"id":"da8c85132b9bd45b3e8415405c753343","text":"A Circulation","correct":false},{"id":"4e4e3ccc157ce52c9ddcf1d7277faf6e","text":"A Distribution","correct":true},{"id":"c680109c8813a5a660a981f781dc0b1e","text":"A Load Balancer","correct":false}]},{"id":"pzjuwu91-24rb-x77o-tzlj-dzpn3pvo3v3v","domain":"security","question":"You need to use an AWS service to assess the security and compliance of your EC2 instances. Which of the following services should you use?","explanation":"AWS Inspector is an automated security assessment service that helps improve the security and compliance of applications deployed on AWS. AWS Trusted Advisor can give security recommendations about your AWS resources, but not within EC2 instances themselves. AWS Shield and WAF can protect EC2 instances, but don't possess any capabilities to assess their security and compliance","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/inspector/?nc2=h_m1","title":"About AWS Inspector"}],"answers":[{"id":"7c90c8f2a24f3a1a28525f19fb2c75ab","text":"AWS Inspector","correct":true},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false},{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false},{"id":"05f43441d2d29ae2bb38fc8596ca6ff7","text":"AWS Trusted Advisor","correct":false}]},{"id":"q9rl4dzm-8wyq-y23f-41wx-15rhrz976akb","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are a collection of datacentres within a specific region?","explanation":"Availability Zones are a collection of datacentres within a specific region.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"1fb6aae6611aa5001c41c1e356609c41","text":"Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"2bdbf4724b81ff0529e32fdb1af28130","text":"AWS Origins","correct":false},{"id":"5948f3347ebc02ebc690227c059661e1","text":"Regions","correct":false},{"id":"17d8fc1e4ceb765476776889d7f6c5ab","text":"Edge Locations","correct":false}]},{"id":"w53824dy-uk0y-a0r6-b6eu-8t2xzl3155or","domain":"tech","question":"Yourself and a colleague both want to create a bucket called \"myawsomebucket\" to store your study notes - will you both be able to do this?","explanation":"As S3 bucket names are global, they need to be globally unique meaning you and your colleague cannot have two buckets with the same name, no matter the circumstances","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/Welcome.html","title":"What Is Amazon S3?"}],"answers":[{"id":"93cba07454f06a4a960172bbd6e2a435","text":"Yes","correct":false},{"id":"3de7dd4f2d662d5eecc35fa4eadaa8c8","text":"Yes, as long as you are using different AWS Regions","correct":false},{"id":"bafd7322c6e97d25b6299b5d6fe8920b","text":"No","correct":true},{"id":"e90d556314ed67ac2dcf70aa2bd7fefd","text":"Yes, as long as you are using different AWS Accounts","correct":false}]},{"id":"110c4336-0571-488d-bc05-fc2fd78887b4","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is the name of AWS Regions designed to allow U.S. government agencies and customers to move significantly sensitive workloads into the cloud?","explanation":"AWS GovCloud is an AWS Region specially designed to host sensitive data and regulated workloads from U.S. government agencies and customers. In addition, it addresses the most stringent U.S. government security and compliance requirements. ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/govcloud-us/","title":"AWS GovCloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"55e430ef34ef9e18d752b0c39ae96c4a","text":"AWS Government Cloud","correct":false},{"id":"ce8b567fad0737a23a7c47b5d781acae","text":"AWS GovRegion","correct":false},{"id":"6f76628274759630f18deb508898fa64","text":"AWS GovCloud","correct":true},{"id":"528af0ceafec0ca0b002f96151614f38","text":"AWS Government Region","correct":false}]},{"id":"rv438cbg-ow9h-jrfd-gxxt-a83ko2ojlo7c","domain":"concepts","question":"In AWS' Global Infrastructure, what are Edge Locations responsible for?","explanation":"Edge Locations host a Content Delivery Network called CloudFront.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"0df5575df91cfdc3471135f97cd57b5b","text":"Providing redundant backup to your AWS services","correct":false},{"id":"e2dd2357c3f760b6df8cd9ef82402a0e","text":"Providing disaster recovery services","correct":false},{"id":"3d5bde6fd721f0872d6ad91a83e073cd","text":"Providing independent power grids to Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"7e293752730d983b3fb263bc37525a5c","text":"Hosting a Content Delivery Network called CloudFront","correct":true}]},{"id":"77471ce7-4336-4912-9c33-ecfc5d174a41","domain":"billing","question":"You want to monitor your costs of using your AWS services and receive alerts when the thresholds you defined are met. Which of the following AWS Budget types should you create?","explanation":"You need to create a cost budget with AWS Budgets if you want to monitor the cost of using your AWS services.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/budgets-managing-costs.html","title":"Managing Your Costs with Budgets"}],"answers":[{"id":"bd4ad96569591af6420d456b8176c90d","text":"Savings Plans Budget","correct":false},{"id":"7d45335a770dd2fc66658fb908bb7f9a","text":"Cost Budget","correct":true},{"id":"3f3eb4d8c9ecc531c5a784bcc5e608b5","text":"Usage Budget","correct":false},{"id":"825a98fa534bb772e00d7b7571f0217f","text":"Reservation Budget","correct":false}]},{"id":"2cae08d8-1bce-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following types of data transfer concerning Amazon EC2 are free?","explanation":"All data transfer in to EC2 instances from the Internet is free. So is data transfer out of EC2 to CloudFront. Data transfer pricing out from EC2 to the Internet is free as long as it does not exceed 1 GB per month. Since this condition is not included in Response B, it isn’t correct.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/on-demand/#Data_Transfer","title":"EC2 Instance Pricing – Data Transfer"}],"answers":[{"id":"2f08e8cef2078b8c6479a4b91faeeec3","text":"Data transfer in to EC2 from the Internet","correct":true},{"id":"9a1bfe89c1c91cf60b45ef77bf406e09","text":"Data transfer out from EC2 to Amazon CloudFront","correct":true},{"id":"3b4e686ed0886b7be7e142139c38eb68","text":"Data transfer out from EC2 to the Internet","correct":false},{"id":"279a4b71d3edd9b515bb71952e1a12c7","text":"Data transfer out from EC2 to AWS GovCloud","correct":false}]},{"id":"19ddf237-f79d-4d25-b0ae-81419166300b","domain":"security","question":"Enabling Amazon GuardDuty automatically grants this service the permission to analyze which of the following data sources?","explanation":"Amazon GuardDuty monitors the security of your AWS environment by analyzing and processing three data sources, which are VPC Flow Logs, AWS CloudTrail event logs, and DNS logs.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/guardduty/latest/ug/what-is-guardduty.html","title":"What is GuardDuty?"}],"answers":[{"id":"8db8c2b0bbd0ff71d1d15bb32f69e3b8","text":"VPC Flow Logs","correct":true},{"id":"da9b46af667cf2279d002b955813bb34","text":"AWS CloudTrail logs","correct":true},{"id":"a70a14359eb44629c70e41470e05570f","text":"DNS query logs","correct":true},{"id":"6b7cef11406f2fff58dcc619a2b7e482","text":"Amazon S3 buckets","correct":false}]},{"id":"7e71f634-1fe3-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following statements are true of Amazon Redshift?","explanation":"Amazon Redshift is AWS’s data warehouse service designed to scale up to petabytes of structured data. Using Redshift, you can create a data warehouse with a set of nodes, which is referred to as a 'cluster'.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/redshift/latest/mgmt/welcome.html","title":"What Is Amazon Redshift?"}],"answers":[{"id":"eae61ac52e73cabeaa3d471e1f2214dd","text":"It is designed for storing petabytes of data.","correct":true},{"id":"1be4b9169c53e2842d313aa2e9fe2bc5","text":"It is a data warehouse service.","correct":true},{"id":"cb8783f4a61d2d6ce45ab561107c68fe","text":"It is used to launch a set of nodes called a Redshift cluster.","correct":true},{"id":"c195feba1b6755cf70b23e85f649bea5","text":"It stores unstructured data.","correct":false}]},{"id":"fb40110c-2ee1-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services can you use to analyze data?","explanation":"Amazon Kinesis is used to analyze data and video streams in real time, and QuickSight is used to analyze visualizations of customer data. So, both are classified as AWS analytics services. By contrast, Amazon Detective analyzes and visualizes security data, and AWS IAM enables the management of access to AWS services and resources securely. So, neither Detective nor IAM are analytics services; they actually fall under the Security, Identity, and Compliance category.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/","title":"Amazon Web Services (AWS)"}],"answers":[{"id":"a86087964fb00f6ae81475d2c8c3c40c","text":"AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)","correct":false},{"id":"12fc352b40e25021e08572ca0f5d2b11","text":"Amazon Detective","correct":false},{"id":"1590671ce414a2deba7ba0a04fef39b3","text":"Amazon Kinesis","correct":true},{"id":"c52be467fd0472e51b0f2acb2f234421","text":"Amazon QuickSight","correct":true}]},{"id":"soqowg2l-ccsj-oaar-j2gb-65fc7woe2nl6","domain":"tech","question":"An EC2 instance in your VPC needs which of the following for the Internet Gateway to route its traffic to the Internet?","explanation":"An EC2 instance in your VPC needs a Public IP address for the Internet Gateway to route its traffic to the Internet","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/using-instance-addressing.html","title":"Amazon EC2 Instance IP Addressing"}],"answers":[{"id":"583ce1b3b402153b5a395ebc25cd0089","text":"C-Name","correct":false},{"id":"e3cf5882b6dd9eb1653cb26ac13e8a18","text":"Public IP address","correct":true},{"id":"e23f7e20cc7858ff4aa638c669cf4bb9","text":"Private IP address","correct":false},{"id":"0aaf2de24270b96d8ba80262b5f3d983","text":"A-Name","correct":false}]},{"id":"382b7116-1f69-11ea-a5e8-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"What is the maximum number of IAM users you can add to an AWS account at the same time?","explanation":"You can add up to 10 users at one time at the IAM console.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_users_create.html","title":"Creating an IAM User in Your AWS Account"}],"answers":[{"id":"98f13708210194c475687be6106a3b84","text":"20","correct":false},{"id":"c4ca4238a0b923820dcc509a6f75849b","text":"1","correct":false},{"id":"e4da3b7fbbce2345d7772b0674a318d5","text":"5","correct":false},{"id":"d3d9446802a44259755d38e6d163e820","text":"10","correct":true}]},{"id":"2c5901f2-c18a-456c-8a19-5d2da6952cec","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are you responsible for when storing data in S3?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model for managed services, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance). When it comes to S3, this includes all aspects of capacity management, therefore it is an AWS responsibility to make sure that they never run out of storage. Replication to another AZ is also AWS's responsibility in an applicable storage tier - note that the question asks for AZ replication - not Regional Replication which would normally be the customer's responsibility to configure. AWS is also responsible for managing data corruption and resolving it if corruption is detected - however if it cannot fix the corruption, or if data is lost, AWS bears no responsibility for the loss - therefore it is a customer's responsibility to make sure there data is backup up as needed - either though versioning in S3, or through 3rd party tools.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/s3/faqs/?nc=sn&loc=7","title":"S3 FAQ - Durability and Data Protection"}],"answers":[{"id":"f3cc93bd6eec33bc0d666a86175524cd","text":"Making sure your data is not corrupted","correct":false},{"id":"96b64de5e30defc9bab2e6592e515b17","text":"Making sure that enough space has been provisioned for your data","correct":false},{"id":"18e8e0efaea5ce9a47da52086c745de7","text":"Making sure there is enough physical storage available for your data","correct":false},{"id":"f5a4db96c8f945bbaddfca968bc66a00","text":"Replicating your data to another Availability Zone if redundancy is needed","correct":false},{"id":"caec507833650a0d1b82cc852d15ea1f","text":"Backing up your data","correct":true}]},{"id":"79925710-1b09-449b-8a8f-51ebb4ae011f","domain":"security","question":"You are setting up an S3 bucket to host a public website. You have uploaded the files for your website to S3 but when clicking on the object url of the file to verify it can be seen you receive the message access denied, you have tried making the file public but the option is not available. What configuration has been missed?","explanation":"To enable the option for selecting an object to be public you first need to disable the Block Public Access setting on the S3 bucket. This setting is in place to prevent accidental configuration of the S3 bucket and objects being visible from anywhere on the internet.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/WebsiteHosting.html","title":"Hosting a Static Website on Amazon S3"}],"answers":[{"id":"2e12d1999c3eb36bf65cfca4200e4a59","text":"Adding a CNAME value to Route53 for the website","correct":false},{"id":"dc91d7c1f9dfd359ce1f57aa8b2eebb9","text":"The IAM user for S3 Public Website Hosting is currently disabled","correct":false},{"id":"f84968f028b1b306769936b96c99902e","text":"Creating and linking an S3 IAM role to your S3 bucket","correct":false},{"id":"0781b9f1fa104477da535d137bd67124","text":"Removing Block Public Access from the bucket","correct":true}]},{"id":"97909ec2-34ad-4743-b7cc-ca2c83c62cc1","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following statements are true of the AWS Free Tier?","explanation":"The AWS Free Tier offers some services for free for the first 12 months after signing up for an AWS account. It also offers free trials of select AWS services for a short period. So, usage is governed by these principles. Although there are some service usages that are always free, this does not apply to EC2 Micro instances nor S3 storage of up to 5 GB.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"f60585d833d73cf82fda96da1f19b3e6","text":"Some AWS services come with short-term free trial offers.","correct":true},{"id":"424553c7a1502a98737dfd15823ee215","text":"Some AWS services are free for the first 12 months following the initial sign-up date to AWS.","correct":true},{"id":"c90c4c865ee803cfa9bbe8e9a2d845c9","text":"Amazon S3 storage of up to 5 GB is always free.","correct":false},{"id":"42c6d3d9032dba4f7aea8ddeedde2f6c","text":"You will never be charged for use of EC2 Micro instances.","correct":false}]},{"id":"57d67272-2fbd-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"What is the maximum amount of storage that Amazon Aurora offers?","explanation":"With each database instance launched in AWS, Aurora can auto-scale up to 64 TB when needed.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/AuroraUserGuide/CHAP_AuroraOverview.html","title":"What Is Amazon Aurora?"}],"answers":[{"id":"70f79b00cb7649d94d473895d6c540d2","text":"1 TB","correct":false},{"id":"074c2f1dacf9047766e7f8d5dce71060","text":"5 GB","correct":false},{"id":"911ede8df5585598c294830dafe276fa","text":"32 GB","correct":false},{"id":"c1edd650c09defc6ca8d0aaf67803ddc","text":"64 TB","correct":true}]},{"id":"1u986u6j-pa4x-orum-u2t7-qu0b9lljqm76","domain":"tech","question":"You need to ensure that you have the correct number of EC2 instances available to handle the load for your application. Which AWS service should you use?","explanation":"Auto Scaling will ensure you have the optimal number of EC2 instances to handle your application's load, based on rules you specify. The other services mentioned can help distribute load amongst existing resources, but do not have the ability by themselves to create new resources.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/autoscaling/","title":"About Auto Scaling"}],"answers":[{"id":"e95e5a2a3cc8625bca3d71b817367e2d","text":"Elastic Load Balancer","correct":false},{"id":"b3b5475001f327d331389c6f07ff7c3a","text":"Application Load Balancer","correct":false},{"id":"37e242ab2d525505933bbdb47d50d2b9","text":"Route53","correct":false},{"id":"afd14eb3f151c84e6ef7ab63812b4fbc","text":"Auto Scaling","correct":true}]},{"id":"bce6da84-1c95-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Upon which of these measurements is AWS Lambda pricing based?","explanation":"With AWS Lambda, you are charged based on the number of requests for your functions and the amount of time (duration) it takes for your code to execute.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lambda/pricing/","title":"AWS Lambda Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"4789f23283b3a61f858b641a1bef19a3","text":"Memory","correct":false},{"id":"a817cbcc67f9a1988581b7d71d401622","text":"Number of requests","correct":true},{"id":"880a586b8b9c63efeba6c7f9afae7dc0","text":"Data transfer","correct":false},{"id":"e02d2ae03de9d493df2b6b2d2813d302","text":"Duration","correct":true}]},{"id":"92196d52-1bd3-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"How many elastic IP addresses can you associate with a running EC2 instance with no charge?","explanation":"An elastic IP address is associated with each AWS account, and they can be associated with a running EC2 instance at no charge. If you associate additional ones, you will have to pay for them.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/elastic-ip-addresses-eip.html","title":"Elastic IP Addresses"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/on-demand/#Data_Transfer","title":"Amazon EC2 Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"c81e728d9d4c2f636f067f89cc14862c","text":"2","correct":false},{"id":"e4da3b7fbbce2345d7772b0674a318d5","text":"5","correct":false},{"id":"d3d9446802a44259755d38e6d163e820","text":"10","correct":false},{"id":"c4ca4238a0b923820dcc509a6f75849b","text":"1","correct":true}]},{"id":"8dmul9q1-wi30-bo4k-81j9-ztcv7dgeoybt","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following EC2 instance types will realize a savings over time in exchange for a contracted term-of-service?","explanation":"EC2 Reserved Instances offer significant discounts for a contracted term-of-service, of up to 75% off. On-Demand instances are charged equally per-hour, regardless of how long they're run for. Spot instances are cheaper than On-Demand instances, but aren't intended for long term use","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"409aa157dda2d7faab6bf2938e322891","text":"Discount instances","correct":false},{"id":"2a80e91907ea76d424690185914b6eae","text":"On-demand instances","correct":false},{"id":"bcc129e8d9496a05a331c903d4c5bcb0","text":"Reserved instances","correct":true},{"id":"991236e27b7cb98a2eeff8897b3e0bb4","text":"Spot instances","correct":false}]},{"id":"b7d5jc0p-zg8y-0hwp-3cjv-2yxp349xk58p","domain":"security","question":"You want to streamline access management for your AWS administrators by assigning them a pre-defined set of permissions based on their job role - which of the below is the best way to approach this?","explanation":"Using IAM Groups lets you create a list of pre-defined permissions that any user made a part of that group will be granted. Roles are primarily used to grant AWS resources permissions to other AWS resources and generally are not for end-users. Amazon Cognito is a service that help authenticate users to your apps, and not the AWS console itself.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_groups.html","title":"IAM Groups"}],"answers":[{"id":"ffc1a593680549bf1bc0e966a70f0683","text":"Use IAM Groups","correct":true},{"id":"28639700aadbc704e3daae5ba44ab388","text":"Use Amazon Cognito","correct":false},{"id":"71f7b94ac76ec4aa2860353bc1120591","text":"Use IAM Roles","correct":false},{"id":"48fb6d39f4c7857dc342d789480a20ea","text":"Use AWS Organizations","correct":false}]},{"id":"nfy6hmhv-trpt-lh3v-z6zh-4icv8kpv7xn6","domain":"concepts","question":"When setting up an Organization in AWS, which of the below is true when selecting which features to enable?","explanation":"With AWS Organizations, Consolidated Billing is always enabled. All other features are either enabled as a group, or disabled as a group - that is, you cannot individually enable or disable a feature - it's all or nothing!","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/en_pv/organizations/latest/userguide/orgs_getting-started_concepts.html","title":"AWS Organizations Terminology and Concepts"}],"answers":[{"id":"ea31b0ef93ed02b05984774a32d72054","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing, then pick which other individual features you want enabled ","correct":false},{"id":"4890bb732d34952682735fd4950bcae8","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing, plus all other features enabled","correct":true},{"id":"fd07b14b5f6a4065154c418c232ecd89","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing disabled, then pick which of the other features you want enabled.","correct":false},{"id":"125540f5091c07ae2a9b7b8c0d95a432","text":"You can select to have just Consolidated Billing enabled","correct":true}]},{"id":"rqfj1uaw-51ci-mvl2-1djk-uzefaek5cehy","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following is correct?","explanation":"The number of Edge Locations is greater than the number of Availability Zones, which is greater than the number of Regions. Regions contain Availability Zones, therefore there will always be more AZs than Regions.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"3782de3e5fc87f6e1a21193778c0d5bf","text":"# of Availability Zones > # of Edge Locations > # of Regions","correct":false},{"id":"27268ba761c3ae0dbf9e4c8959f13e0f","text":"# of Availability Zones > # of Regions > # of Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"07ebe9ccf5e5396c2f2c81de53d3829e","text":"# of Regions > # of Availability Zones > # of Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"916cfd186ad7a451ebd785b35c738429","text":"# of Edge Locations > # of Availability Zones > # of Regions","correct":true}]},{"id":"71sehgn8-lx4k-034j-srs9-vv6xhd7w10qh","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are principles of sound design when it comes to performance efficiency?","explanation":"Of these choices, you should democratize advanced technologies, deploy into multiple Regions, and use Serverless technologies.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"e891a453952de1898dde71f36801790a","text":"Use Serverless architectures.","correct":true},{"id":"c25dea02447eef08ddb2affdbb171485","text":"Mechanical empathy","correct":false},{"id":"db3e408a0aa09a4e83bdace8a1e57fcc","text":"Deploy into multiple Regions to go global in minutes.","correct":true},{"id":"56110ec02fe5d9a3ae8e5a69af838158","text":"Have your IT staff master all new technologies.","correct":false},{"id":"8c3a4b8048462b1877e2da598308fe3a","text":"Democratize advanced technologies.","correct":true}]},{"id":"4f5e27aa-65cf-46da-9db4-42b569eb0d05","domain":"tech","question":"Your employer, a major digital media company, needs you to implement an AWS service that delivers its dynamic web content worldwide, relying on edge locations to improve latency. Which one of the following services should you pick to accomplish that?","explanation":"CloudWatch monitors AWS resources and applications, CloudTrail increases visibility into user and resource activity, and there is no AWS service named CloudConnect. It is CloudFront that functions as Amazon’s content delivery network, which is a system of distributed servers for delivering web content to users.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudfront/","title":"Amazon CloudFront"}],"answers":[{"id":"92fbbd5478621cf8f70624389759b44c","text":"CloudTrail","correct":false},{"id":"e45b2ed303bc7e3b63b82e4766fd7d8b","text":"CloudConnect","correct":false},{"id":"311bdda432aba736b8dcb987523c0c92","text":"CloudWatch","correct":false},{"id":"bef6cb89241de238f082cb243307ad1b","text":"CloudFront","correct":true}]},{"id":"1keyzmwc-3y04-sr9m-mv2x-5662cst34a1u","domain":"tech","question":"What is the maximum number of objects you can store in S3 per AWS account?","explanation":"You can store an essentially unlimited number of objects in S3 - either in a single bucket or across multiple in your account","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/BucketRestrictions.html","title":"S3 Bucket Restrictions and Limitations"}],"answers":[{"id":"ffbf4e2174ca393ee1db3d508a85867c","text":"1,048,576","correct":false},{"id":"545f6c2f382c04810103b3e5e6f7d841","text":"Unlimited","correct":true},{"id":"1eb974a1c586444002352cbc05918056","text":"262,144","correct":false},{"id":"c8b11bc1bd64f9dfaba4a8f3954d8401","text":"65,536","correct":false}]},{"id":"el8zebxq-qo1d-az5o-l4lp-vmh132hnt1zd","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following Compliance guarantees attests to the fact that the AWS Platform has met the standard required for the secure storage of medical records in the US?","explanation":"A HIPAA certification attests to the fact that the AWS Platform has met the standard required for the secure storage of medical records in the US.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/pci-data-privacy-protection-hipaa-soc-fedramp-faqs/","title":"AWS Compliance"},{"url":"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hippa_(disambiguation)","title":"HIPPA or HIPAA"}],"answers":[{"id":"393dceb94f2cac456fd53985a67d72b3","text":"HITECH","correct":false},{"id":"d0a785d52ac4a841f7efdf0098d9ebd5","text":"HIPAA","correct":true},{"id":"dba5359496e7ea71f51ce4da1ee614bd","text":"GLBA","correct":false},{"id":"739f96badcfca6fd03c1e5b17971c9de","text":"HIPPO","correct":false},{"id":"827ec26130c30cc52e3fb178e0ef505c","text":"FERPA","correct":false}]},{"id":"90df786a-99f7-45c0-b4ed-126bfc6c55de","domain":"concepts","question":"A mobile shopping list app needs to be able to add, delete, and update items on specific lists anytime a user desires. The backend for the app will run on Amazon EC2 instances with Auto Scaling to manage fluctuations in user demand. Many times, a user will perform maintenance on many list items in a single session. What design characteristic must be incorporated into the app for these requirements to be met?","explanation":"In order for horizontal scaling to be effective, you'll want to make sure the app doesn't store previous transaction or session information on specific EC2 instances. That way, any EC2 instance provisioned by Auto Scaling can process the request. Leveraging load balancing is also a good practice, but doesn't address the need for a stateless app. Session affinity goes the other direction, directing a load balancer to route transactions to a specific instance each time. Bootstrapping runs scripts each time an EC2 instance is provisioned.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud - AWS Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"712738cb3dbc4b4aeb218af7b44b731c","text":"Use bootstrapping on the EC2 instances","correct":false},{"id":"175dc87c438249634b2c6104864a2e6a","text":"Leverage load balancing to distribute transactions to multiple nodes","correct":false},{"id":"7f3d1559e229505103abfd9297d2249c","text":"Make sure the app doesn’t need knowledge of previous transactions","correct":true},{"id":"3169165ef00c3474aa673628039e0dc1","text":"Implement session affinity","correct":false}]},{"id":"2df4774c-2e69-4156-96c5-b1efbfba754f","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the below is correct when looking at Regions, Availability Zones, Edge Location and Datacentres?","explanation":"Regions contain two or more Availability Zones, which are themselves made up of one or more Datacentres. This means there will always be more AZs than Regions. Edge locations are separate from AZs and Regions, and there are more Edge Locations than Regions and Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/?p=ngi&loc=2","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"f4b49cc5b3d286cd78cac99f03cecce3","text":"There are more Regions than Availability zones","correct":false},{"id":"f35fa3c5e765907efd6efa66bc1741c3","text":"The number of Availability Zones is the same as the number of Regions","correct":false},{"id":"29030db1d3f86fea8d8779a9c964c207","text":"There are more Availability Zones than Edge locations","correct":false},{"id":"26c658a3c4aee0122f0178a65f0ea80b","text":"There are more Availability Zones then Regions","correct":true}]},{"id":"j55neiwz-9leq-mmdm-z3qb-rjp9ll7te3ey","domain":"tech","question":"By default, what can a Private Subnet communicate with?","explanation":"By default, a Private Subnet can only communicate with other subnets in the same VPC, be they Private or Public. In order to communicate to the internet, a NAT Gateway and Internet Gateway are required, and to enable communication between subnets in different VPCs the VPCs must first be peered.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonVPC/latest/UserGuide/VPC_Subnets.html#vpc-subnet-basics","title":"VPC and Subnet Basics"}],"answers":[{"id":"2833f376428e487505135ddd3e3dfa83","text":"Other Private Subnets in the same VPC","correct":true},{"id":"6aff3455ef4ee9f91852d846278af179","text":"Private Subnets in a different VPC","correct":false},{"id":"fc10601fc9c6d89cc325196b308a5d09","text":"Public Subnets in a different VPC","correct":false},{"id":"bc073365b9c1fbd0626a854e3b600009","text":"The internet","correct":false},{"id":"8d6c6a7fbfb26a46f1cb21637cb6efc6","text":"Public Subnets in the same VPC","correct":true}]},{"id":"aabc59b3-b883-454e-8336-dac6f49eb7c3","domain":"security","question":"You are a Systems Administrator who has just started adding IAM users to your company’s AWS account. However, you worry that the users will not create passwords strong enough to prevent unauthorized access. What is the most reliable way to ensure that users are using strong passwords?","explanation":"Use Identity and Access Management (IAM) to apply an IAM password policy. While awareness and training are critical to developing good security practices, the most reliable option is to use an IAM Password Policy, which won't allow users to use lower strength passwords.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_credentials_passwords_account-policy.html?icmpid=docs_iam_console","title":"Setting an Account Password Policy for IAM Users"}],"answers":[{"id":"2ef38712519600d72d012e44a6dcb5a3","text":"Ask for the password of each user and create a much stronger one by yourself.","correct":false},{"id":"da197ad4fa2d98027feab02afd84d7fc","text":"Speak with each IAM user individually about the importance of creating strong passwords.","correct":false},{"id":"6cb5679faafdf0c247c2543bdca0e635","text":"Apply an IAM password policy to ensure users create appropriately strong passwords.","correct":true},{"id":"a08ccc3650b327c02cd13367d8ffa875","text":"Hold an AWS webinar to stress the importance of creating strong passwords.","correct":false}]},{"id":"eaf197bf-a9f1-4611-90be-dbcf7364c74a","domain":"concepts","question":"You have an application load balancer for routing traffic from developers to the EC2 instance that contains a web application being put into operation. To prepare for the application going live for public use, you add an Auto Scaling Group and a second application load balancer to route web traffic from customers to the EC2 instance. The addition is an example of which of the following:","explanation":"This is an example of scalability, which means that systems are expected to grow over time with no drop in performance. ","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"2166e76dc88d642260416a536b06a412","text":"Durability","correct":false},{"id":"820b8f74ad843d1574106ec4cadfc07e","text":"Reliability","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false}]},{"id":"bcc6x5vm-wlrp-z3vu-k77q-nltdaem9w8ep","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is not database service in AWS?","explanation":"Amazon EBS is a storage service providing virtual hard disks in the cloud, while the other services listed are database services.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/products/databases/","title":"AWS Databases"}],"answers":[{"id":"f7415e33f972c03abd4f3fed36748f7a","text":"Amazon Redshift","correct":false},{"id":"69670a9d53817d1ec89e685997343ce2","text":"Amazon Aurora","correct":false},{"id":"516729a7c0562425406a22cfe6a2c163","text":"Amazon EBS","correct":true},{"id":"bacabc9e09c314ac47bb30bd2f431cf4","text":"Amazon Neptune","correct":false}]},{"id":"bcecb806-dc3d-42d5-abaf-92b78f78bf00","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are TRUE statements when it comes to network security for an EC2 instance in AWS?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance) and software required to deliver the service. In this scenario, AWS is responsible for the underlying network hardware, not the customer. However the customer is responsible for ensuring that only wanted, valid traffic reaches their EC2 instance through the use of Security Groups, Access Control Lists or Software Firewalls","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"e61949c2c6f3b07d6b052aeed05cafd5","text":"AWS is responsible for ensuring unwanted traffic does not reach the EC2 instance","correct":false},{"id":"1dbd0eb41e4e90508191eb1f5a99b615","text":"The customer is responsible for ensuring unwanted traffic does not reach the EC2 instance","correct":true},{"id":"d06119c27ec0a4e3b321bd66da22fea2","text":"AWS is responsible for ensuring malicious traffic does not reach the EC2 instance","correct":false},{"id":"3bab15fdca03e0fc9fcb17e344d1ffed","text":"The customer is responsible for ensuring malicious traffic does not impair the network hardware","correct":false},{"id":"4aa6ca9653c0c4e24ff62399d1e4ca09","text":"The customer is responsible for ensuring malicious traffic does not reach the EC2 instance","correct":true},{"id":"01407b8624848ffc3a63fcbb919421fb","text":"AWS is responsible for ensuring malicious traffic does not impair the network hardware","correct":true}]},{"id":"b386cdc3-9626-47e1-9be3-a4d78c363ad4","domain":"security","question":"Instead of relying on a single data center to provide its services across the world, AWS relies on several physical locations, each of which consists of one or more data centers. What are the official names for these physical locations and data centers?","explanation":"The physical locations from which AWS provides its services are known as Regions. Each Region consists of at least two Availability Zone, which can have anywhere from one data center to several of them.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/","title":"Global Infrastructures Regions and AZs"}],"answers":[{"id":"fb27078790943273979b82fd00f61dd1","text":" Sections; Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"2015015e824f6bbbc098e8b097d2dbda","text":"Regions; data centers","correct":false},{"id":"c4bc6e143511ce56ce0ac41624e4c370","text":"Regions; Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"02da4e23b021b2dfa7ed963444ab3325","text":"Locations; data centers","correct":false}]},{"id":"a87b87a1-e801-e917-756a-a78256b2945c","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following is a Shared Control of the AWS Shared Responsibility Model?","explanation":"Shared Controls are elements of the Shared Responsibility Model where both AWS and the customer have shared responsibilities within their own contexts. Awareness & Training is a Shared Control, since AWS trains AWS employees, but a customer must train their own employees. Datacentre Security is solely the responsibility of AWS. Configuration of an Application within an EC2 instance, and Identity and Access Management remain the responsibility of the customer","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"4fde53f82fbc6748a0e6b9b51f615287","text":"Datacentre Security","correct":false},{"id":"e40133007bfa03149696a52e6c45b8d9","text":"EC2 Instance Application Configuration","correct":false},{"id":"791716f366839a73d41b8ac1ae95bad0","text":"Identity and Access Management","correct":false},{"id":"027e815b818f136c5892cd32b9f87ddd","text":"Awareness & Training","correct":true}]},{"id":"d5512a42-0f94-11ea-8d71-362b9e155667","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services enable you to continuously monitor and record configuration changes of your resources?","explanation":"It can be easy to confuse Config and CloudTrail, since both are AWS management-and-governance tools. However, they operate differently. While CloudTrail provides event history of your AWS account activity, Config specifically focuses on listing the resources in your AWS account and presenting their configuration change history.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/config/","title":"AWS Config"}],"answers":[{"id":"621f4719cc9f27432c4c095f76df474e","text":"Amazon GuardDuty","correct":false},{"id":"2d80a80d60fea86242f99512dbac7529","text":"AWS Config","correct":true},{"id":"26ca9b29af36f84c577a85a80a58a381","text":"AWS CloudTrail","correct":false},{"id":"05f43441d2d29ae2bb38fc8596ca6ff7","text":"AWS Trusted Advisor","correct":false}]},{"id":"e4306810-2a64-4eb4-9c58-431ea8a91190","domain":"tech","question":"A software development team needs to create numerous testing environments each day based on multiple concurrent project activities. Provisioning of these environments needs to happen within minutes to ensure that project deadlines are met. The number of environments needed daily varies depending shifting priorities in business requirements. How can the team best achieve the agility they need for creating the testing environments?","explanation":"AWS CloudFormation provides templates to specify all the AWS resources needed by the testing environments. These templates can be instantiated as stacks to provision consistent environments every time one is needed. AWS Auto Scaling will only handle the EC2 instances, and expands and contracts instances based on policies. AWS Systems Manager is useful for system administration tasks, and AWS Lambda has run-time limitations.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudformation/","title":"AWS CloudFormation"}],"answers":[{"id":"d9a6df6805662c26de87001a1d7b5ae4","text":"Use AWS Systems Manager Automation to provision and de-provision the testing environments","correct":false},{"id":"d0251c104fe180cf808a23905d11ab7c","text":"Leverage AWS Auto Scaling to expand and contract the testing server pool based on demand","correct":false},{"id":"7eab42e9ed95a6b8f6eba51c1d6ba41e","text":"Have AWS CloudFormation provision the stacks and resources needed for the testing environments","correct":true},{"id":"5a6510861bc8f77b0a75412925312eff","text":"Invoke AWS Lambda functions to run the test scenarios","correct":false}]},{"id":"d05a0228-8d82-4cef-8dfb-4e2cb3856a9f","domain":"security","question":"According to the Shared Responsibility Model, which of the following is AWS responsible for?","explanation":"Protecting the infrastructure that runs all of the services in the AWS Cloud is the responsibility of AWS. Such services include EC2 infrastructure - the hardware compute platform for running EC2 instances and Amazon Virtual Private Cloud, or VPC, which enables customers to provision a logically isolated section of the AWS Cloud to launch their resources. The subnets, security groups, and network access control lists configured in the VPC are the responsibility of the customer.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/vpc/","title":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"06ea336ee4a57004a721e76f5cdd9083","text":"Network Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":false},{"id":"74cd215a46d2bd96fc35dad7ef313283","text":"Subnets","correct":false},{"id":"c33dcb724e4d74e54dbc8347d4402690","text":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud","correct":true},{"id":"28aaf85b7ba1e63aa22c1c645a4c22e4","text":"Elastic Cloud Compute (EC2) infrastructure","correct":true}]},{"id":"8r7r7n13-hvyw-63f9-gltg-21wwwmux0grq","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes a system that will remain operational even in the event of a component failure?","explanation":"a fault-tolerant system will remain operational even in the event of a component failure.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/whitepapers/designing-fault-tolerant-applications/","title":"Building Fault-Tolerant Applications in the AWS Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"28cb2468ce3a85b4d10668ec48f5e4d6","text":"Scalable","correct":false},{"id":"9818cb0bfa2dfb200a8c078b1fe1c2fd","text":"Highly Available","correct":false},{"id":"a078ed5ade8df4aac54efbdb57e63ad2","text":"Elastic","correct":false},{"id":"7bf4251c070de07f503b12b9d341daea","text":"Fault-tolerant","correct":true}]},{"id":"9n50o6rz-03s4-bpbd-i7dy-36qby4h0ka5x","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are you responsible for when running an RDS database on AWS?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model for managed services, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance), as well as making sure the underlying OS and application is up to date. You as the user are responsible for keeping your data secure.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"86da12905838c932b65844a3fa01aa08","text":"Updating the operating system","correct":false},{"id":"2b6b76aaf679124f3da7b20c5df23923","text":"Updating the database software","correct":false},{"id":"8782b4a6bdea28cea082df1413a7f818","text":"Controlling access to the compute hardware","correct":false},{"id":"57b862a3c428d3330f8c03216acd2c16","text":"Controlling access to the database","correct":true},{"id":"0266c79a8678f6881cc2857043b46509","text":"Controlling access to the network hardware","correct":false}]},{"id":"nncwnx24-taau-zgsd-blel-newfprz6u93i","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are principles of sound design when it comes to security?","explanation":"The AWS Cloud includes many design patterns and architectural options that you can apply to a wide variety of use cases. Some key design principles of sound design when it comes to security include: Apply security to all layers, enable tracability, and implement the principal of least privlidge options.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/apn/the-5-pillars-of-the-aws-well-architected-framework/","title":"The 5 Pillars of the AWS Well-Architected Framework"}],"answers":[{"id":"4bb4d3eefe3829a2b20a099180702f9f","text":"Apply security at all layers.","correct":true},{"id":"d0f7903229df2e315b9c9561f18a4b7c","text":"Secure your physical resources.","correct":false},{"id":"718831eabf7a4582f906032cd06bcea7","text":"Implement the Principle of Least Privilege","correct":true},{"id":"ff94370d49b79e8817f49bbbc97dbf02","text":"Apply security to your application only.","correct":false},{"id":"214beb729ce64f08fe84798c5bbedd6f","text":"Enable traceability.","correct":true}]},{"id":"4hjaxq6n-z5w0-zfz5-rhia-l14kd19r6656","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are best practices when it comes to securing your AWS account?","explanation":"Creating individual IAM users, using groups to assign them permission and creating a strong password policy are all key components of securing your AWS account. The root user should only be used in emergencies, therefore there should be no need to have Root Access Keys which allow the root user Programmatic access - any Programmatic access should use something other than the root account. It is not possible to delete the root password, and this should be securely, safely stored and not used in any applications!","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_root-user.html","title":"The AWS Account Root User"}],"answers":[{"id":"07623cbc5a5f07bde8c94a98256a165f","text":"Use groups to assign permissions.","correct":true},{"id":"5d44464e3d76ef6a6641b8044d7d2525","text":"Activate MFA on the Root Account.","correct":true},{"id":"561f3fa869736d8c37dd07fc1284f00f","text":"Delete your Root access keys.","correct":true},{"id":"427d69ad60aa7d9c68a9214e103fc80a","text":"Delete your Root account password.","correct":false},{"id":"b109f832528a7df4db93f8f1016812b4","text":"Create individual IAM users.","correct":true},{"id":"9c2eddf5402bf5f69b4cfd6f6cbb82ef","text":"Store your Root account keys on your application for easy access.","correct":false},{"id":"af5257e2e32921faab688050c9de091e","text":"Apply an IAM password policy.","correct":true}]},{"id":"hmh7tnlm-n4hf-9v8o-75e5-uksbwqwddinx","domain":"tech","question":"For which of the below is S3 a suitable storage solution?","explanation":"S3 is object storage suitable for the storage of 'flat' files like documents, photos, etc. Use cases which require very atomic or consistent reading and writing, such as databases and operating systems, are more suited to EBS (Elastic Block Store) storage.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/s3/","title":"About S3"}],"answers":[{"id":"ea2ef9b0d095bf991f4973633b485340","text":"Databases","correct":false},{"id":"b11ddc7e1671c0bd22dc89dd757508d4","text":"Pictures","correct":true},{"id":"aab338915e32b60e92c8de3a23aa5c5d","text":"Operating Systems","correct":false},{"id":"f28128b38efbc6134dc40751ee21fd29","text":"Documents","correct":true}]},{"id":"cf545dc9-39ca-4eec-869f-0d416b59aa1f","domain":"concepts","question":"Adding resources to your application as user demand grows is an example of which cloud concept?","explanation":"Scalability is the concept that as cloud has essentially limitless capacity, it allows you to expand out as needed - as detailed in the question. Automation relates to simplyfying common repeated tasks and removing the human element. Although elasticity (the ability to go up and down in resources as needed) is related, this question specifically ask for in in response to user demand, which is closer to Scalability. High Availability relates to the ability of your application to withstand failures in Cloud Infrastructure.","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":false},{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false}]},{"id":"16rz9iw6-s5av-nrg1-1gja-89cbrnwj8uco","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are storage services?","explanation":"VPC is a Networking service, and RDS is a Database service, leaving S3 and Elastic File System as the storage services","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/efs/","title":"About EFS"}],"answers":[{"id":"1dbd7e466350bb810a3ea48be7668773","text":"AWS Elastic File System","correct":true},{"id":"94a6c127c422f3501ac2fd0084ebbd25","text":"AWS VPC","correct":false},{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":true},{"id":"6e11595bc7ccdbf672fefaababf72939","text":"AWS RDS","correct":false}]},{"id":"3edc2ffd-d684-4cf1-83f9-b782b6782711","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following pricing models are available for EC2?","explanation":"EC2 has four different pricing models, On Demand, Reserved, Spot and Dedicated Hosts. Each pricing model has been created for different workload types and use cases.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"942d4e37dd5607ab68e54755540d4a47","text":"Reserved","correct":true},{"id":"acbe4e201e8e2ac67830983f9c8d7970","text":"Dedicated Hosts","correct":true},{"id":"a687560297f056cb18ffb527b46f79b4","text":"Dot Instances","correct":false},{"id":"abf84cb49aaf1ec8157f80e4d27d011e","text":"Hybrid Instances","correct":false},{"id":"244492cdce9dce0555c52ebe1182e0a3","text":"On Demand","correct":true}]},{"id":"d29bb03a-1a55-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"According to the AWS Shared Responsibility Model, which of the following is the customer responsible for? (Choose 3)","explanation":"AWS is responsible for protecting the infrastructure that runs its services. Such services include Amazon VPC, which enables a customer to provision a logically isolated section of the AWS Cloud. This section is simply referred to as a virtual private cloud, or VPC. So, while AWS is responsible for the software (Amazon VPC), the customer is responsible for the virtual network created with that software (VPC), as well as whatever goes in it. This includes subnets (each of which consist of a range of IP addresses) and security groups (each of which acts as a virtual firewall to control inbound and outbound traffic).","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/what-is-amazon-vpc.html","title":"What Is Amazon VPC?"}],"answers":[{"id":"1d7c6a62b7a045346e19186c911b38a1","text":"Amazon VPC Service","correct":false},{"id":"452be8d0a4b871d9b4ec8f7e323a17a2","text":"Virtual Private Clouds (VPCs)","correct":true},{"id":"9175bb34d0aede26315b313b9432bcbb","text":"Security groups","correct":true},{"id":"74cd215a46d2bd96fc35dad7ef313283","text":"Subnets","correct":true}]},{"id":"332dccb8-1a46-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following CIDR block size ranges applies to IPv4 addresses in Amazon VPC?","explanation":"For IPv4 addresses, the VPC CIDR block size can be anywhere from /16 to /28.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/vpc-ip-addressing.html","title":"IP Addressing in Your VPC"}],"answers":[{"id":"b23abf46c1e7e117251291617bac5c56","text":"/8 to /36","correct":false},{"id":"699292f46538d2bf62bace8334097bb6","text":"1/ to /40","correct":false},{"id":"d312bf1a99a33142c6a946375494aa20","text":"/12 to /32","correct":false},{"id":"30575066a7baaedf5c35a22bc44a6964","text":"/16 to /28","correct":true}]},{"id":"f3458221-d64a-4bbb-b337-65aa47b1614e","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following does Amazon assure will happen when paying for AWS on an as-needed basis?","explanation":"Amazon provides certain benefits when you pay for services on an as-needed basis for your business. You can spend more time innovating and inventing, which consequently reduces the complexity of procurement and enables your business to be fully elastic. ","links":[{"url":"https://d0.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws_pricing_overview.pdf","title":"How AWS Pricing Works"}],"answers":[{"id":"4657fb4ee914ab51c07ee5913b69cb48","text":"Reducing procurement complexity","correct":true},{"id":"d2c91d7ba7466b41bdbcd42e13db2ecb","text":"Spending more money in the long term","correct":false},{"id":"805b488dc48f4591141569966cee0a89","text":"Enabling the full elasticity of business operations","correct":true},{"id":"8c0088e02946138166ef2d9e4bf9ab82","text":"Spending less money in the long term","correct":false},{"id":"48a2453a766bcd12a90a271271ca86a5","text":"Redirecting focus to innovation and invention","correct":true}]},{"id":"1638290e-2fb4-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following does AWS use to notify you by email when you exceed 85% of your Free Tier limits for each service?","explanation":"AWS uses Budgets to notify you when you exceed 85% of your Free Tier limits for each service you’re using by sending you an email. Picking Cost Explorer as the answer is misleading; it is actually a visualizer you can use to analyze your spend, but it does not alert you on your Free Tier usage. Organizations centralizes the management of your resources; it has nothing to do with usage alerts. And Personal Health Dashboard allows you to visualize the status, rather than usage, of your resources.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/tracking-free-tier-usage.html","title":"Tracking Your Free Tier Usage"}],"answers":[{"id":"c7f176d72688fd87853e31b84159d541","text":"AWS Cost Explorer","correct":false},{"id":"e32a801c8e0beab6abb9361e937365be","text":"AWS Budgets","correct":true},{"id":"d189bb1b260dc3da48b6e6f5e1ec6879","text":"AWS Personal Health Dashboard","correct":false},{"id":"b1820ee1cf68e2e65f263ff7bb207626","text":"AWS Organizations","correct":false}]},{"id":"338d1783-ff92-46f0-b582-c4bb314efcff","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is the collection of tools used for developing and managing applications on AWS?","explanation":"Software Development Kits, or SDKs, provide everything you need to develop and manage applications in AWS, including the programming language of your choice.","links":[{"url":"https://d0.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws-overview.pdf","title":"Overview of Amazon Web Services"}],"answers":[{"id":"4b77a7b9a57e83d2c4b01e16f3234143","text":"Command Line Interface","correct":false},{"id":"a3b73fb1194d31eec199838e4fc4c08a","text":"AWS Management Console","correct":false},{"id":"41942dbedbefdea8b52c300f0dc777d0","text":"Programming Languages","correct":false},{"id":"0654ac3bb453dcb388c05bee59caa0be","text":"Software Development Kits","correct":true}]},{"id":"520b9022-2fa7-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Your company needs the support of concierge-level account specialists to help with billing and account subjects. Which of the following AWS Support pricing plans provides that feature?","explanation":"Only the Enterprise support plan will provide a Concierge Support Team, which is a group of account specialists to assist your company with their billing and accounting questions.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","title":"AWS Support Plans"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/enterprise/","title":"AWS Enterprise Support"}],"answers":[{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false}]},{"id":"vikk5xb3-er5k-f530-xnql-upfbhr4zjhvv","domain":"concepts","question":"How many Availability Zones does each Region have?","explanation":"Normal Regions are made up of at least 2 Availability Zones to allow for highly available architectures in the cloud. The actual number of AZs can vary per Region.  There is a special class of Region called a 'Local Region' that have only 1 AZ, however that is viewed as an abnormal case by AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"57ca7c66f61abc17eb42ff90f5bed87e","text":"At least 2","correct":true},{"id":"f3f74d2863be40169cddca9e902304f3","text":"At least 3","correct":false},{"id":"32cf9ef8a3f23b762138a410b9f02129","text":"Only 1","correct":false},{"id":"61f2018e5a51be7a751ae1eb61c1f017","text":"Regions don't have Availability Zones, Availability Zones have Regions","correct":false}]},{"id":"4nktsg9p-4zj3-dwhq-6y42-7tns3wptn2q7","domain":"tech","question":"You need a managed, low-cost relational database for your e-commerce store. Which of the following should you use?","explanation":"RDS is your best option: it's a low-cost, managed database solution. DynamoDB is a non-relational database, and not suitable for this scenario","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/","title":"About RDS"}],"answers":[{"id":"7fe48e833035175294ec48b4086b24e0","text":"AWS ElastiCache","correct":false},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"58dbd4ac6f5e40d5300757915fa51606","text":"MySQL on EC2","correct":false},{"id":"0f41d6f36f8eaee87ea08d9f4b1159e2","text":"RDS","correct":true}]},{"id":"768b0aa8-1fea-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Upon sign-up of an AWS account, how much Amazon S3 Standard storage will you get for no cost?","explanation":"When you sign up for an AWS account, you will get 5 GB of standard S3 storage for the first 12 months under the AWS Free Tier.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/?all-free-tier.sort-by=item.additionalFields.SortRank&all-free-tier.sort-order=asc","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"b3dd42c7956751be5d38b5c0cb2e09c0","text":"5 TB","correct":false},{"id":"70f79b00cb7649d94d473895d6c540d2","text":"1 TB","correct":false},{"id":"0d642755e7f12f7563e3db33bd0c39cb","text":"1 GB","correct":false},{"id":"3a6d03856b824be771cdd922375d59db","text":"20 GB","correct":false},{"id":"074c2f1dacf9047766e7f8d5dce71060","text":"5 GB","correct":true}]},{"id":"84d8ac20-2fb5-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Once you exceed a usage percentage of Free Tier limits for any service, AWS will automatically send you an email notification. What is that percentage?","explanation":"If you exceed 85% of Free Tier usage, AWS will automatically send you an email to notify you. This is to alert you to help with staying within the Free Tier limits; otherwise, you may incur charges.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/tracking-free-tier-usage.html","title":"Tracking Your Free Tier Usage"}],"answers":[{"id":"d09bf41544a3365a46c9077ebb5e35c3","text":"75","correct":false},{"id":"c0c7c76d30bd3dcaefc96f40275bdc0a","text":"50","correct":false},{"id":"1c383cd30b7c298ab50293adfecb7b18","text":"35","correct":false},{"id":"3ef815416f775098fe977004015c6193","text":"85","correct":true}]},{"id":"0mdd9dnl-ji3o-hjum-lyr4-wtpoks65v0z9","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following statements about AWS Region is true?","explanation":"A region is a geographical area divided into Availability Zones. Each region contains at least two publicly accessible Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"bec481a5e2c63bfc93d4922d5845bd2b","text":"Regions are only available in some locations globally","correct":false},{"id":"fddc13d769887bc62fc14c8d844e1aa9","text":"Regions are generally specific geographical areas","correct":true},{"id":"1c52cae4b07ea355b6bf0d1522efc7e7","text":"Regions are made up of Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"2cf30d8c571fe080cdd53d0a78db5689","text":"Regions are automatically fully synchronized to contain the same data globally","correct":false}]},{"id":"n7rouwfc-9cnc-mywz-rj44-v3c021ws4ry3","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following acts like built-in firewalls per instance for your virtual servers?","explanation":"Security Groups act like built-in firewalls for your virtual servers - the rules you create define what is allowed to talk to your instances and how. Although Network Access Control Lists can be used to block or deny traffic, these operate at the subnet level - covering all instances in the subnet with the same ruleset, not per-instance as the question specifies. Route tables tell traffic where it should go next to reach its destination, and an Availability Zone is a collection of datacentres - which isn't relevant in this question. ","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/using-network-security.html","title":"Amazon EC2 Security Groups"}],"answers":[{"id":"8f36276b8cef5979b167a77e143d894e","text":"Route Tables","correct":false},{"id":"1fb6aae6611aa5001c41c1e356609c41","text":"Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":true},{"id":"06ea336ee4a57004a721e76f5cdd9083","text":"Network Access Control Lists","correct":false}]},{"id":"1978e26b-04e4-45ca-8a47-205e50d96c7f","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the below is correct when looking at Regions, Availability Zones, Edge Location and Datacentres?","explanation":"Regions contain two or more Availability Zones, which are themselves made up of one or more Datacentres. Edge locations are a part of AWS' content distribution network, and are seperate from Regions and AZs.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/?p=ngi&loc=2","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"cd6f4614de9281b97b511a1f3f534e8c","text":"Edge Locations contain Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"988326895b235b7a5f2b7eea1a9838f5","text":"Regions contain Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"22d0cb7092012aea1123fcbd58c6519c","text":"Data Centres contain Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"23b72701776466936b717d47eb3be164","text":"Availability Zones contain Data Centres","correct":true}]}]}}}}
